Contact

Rawalpindi, Pakistan 03467493423 (Mobile) waleed.alisarwar336@outlook .com

www.linkedin.com/in/waleed-alisarwar (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Model-View-Controller (MVC)
Databases
Microsoft Copilot

Languages

Punjabi (Elementary)
Urdu (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Basic Formulas and Functions in Microsoft Excel

Getting started with Flutter Development

Microsoft Front-End Developer Professional Certificate

New Horizons Genome Editing

How To Edit Viral Shorts In CapCut

Waleed Ali Sarwar

Call Center Executive | CCE @ Ufone4G | PTCLGroup | Bioinformatics Student @ VU | Aspiring Fullstack web developer Rawalpindi District, Puniab, Pakistan

Summary

Currently pursuing a Bachelor of Science in Bioinformatics at VU and working full-time as a Call Center Executive at Ufone4G - PTCLGroup, I strive to balance academic growth with professional experience.

My role at Ufone4G has strengthened my ability to communicate effectively, solve problems efficiently, and manage tasks in a dynamic environment.

Alongside this, my education has introduced me to scientific concepts such as DNA analysis, PCR techniques, and biochemistry, Database management system, programming essential, Design.

Experience

Ufone 4G
Call Center Executive
September 2024 - Present (7 months)
Islamabad, Islāmābād, Pakistan

In this role, Helpline of Domino's project, focusing on efficient customer order taking, complaint resolution, and enhancing customer relationship management.

My responsibilities included accurately processing orders, addressing customer concerns, and ensuring positive interactions to boost satisfaction and loyalty. Additionally, I actively utilized customer relationship management (CRM) systems to placing an order, track interactions, and follow up on inquiries to deliver a seamless and satisfying customer experience.

This experience strengthened my communication, problem-solving skills, and my ability to work in a fast-paced environment.

Salitex Marketing Team September 2024 - September 2024 (1 month)

Rawalpindi, Punjab, Pakistan

KFC Pakistan Team Member November 2022 - June 2024 (1 year 8 months) Islamabad, Islāmābād, Pakistan

Next Web Lines
Data Entry Specialist
December 2023 - January 2024 (2 months)
Rawalpindi, Punjab, Pakistan

Leads Expert Group Customer Service Representative August 2020 - September 2020 (2 months) Rawalpindi, Punjab, Pakistan

Our duty is to ask customers who are over the age of 70 about their health insurance while they are living in the United States. If they are eligible, then we transfer them to a licensed agent. That's our job from my side.

Education

Virtual University of Pakistan

Bachelor of Science - BS, Bioinformatics · (February 2022)

Government shahbaz shareef Associate college Rawalpindi Intermediate ICS, Computer Science · (April 2019 - February 2021)

Al-Siddeeq Model High School Rawalpindi Matriculation, Science (March 2016 - March 2018)